<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Movies>
    <movie name="Inside-Out">
        <title>Inside Out</title>
        <review>I waited several weeks before going to see Inside Out and therefore was inundated with opinions from various sources by that time. Most of those opinion's being that the movie was the best movie in the universe and everyone cried. Needless to say, my expectations were high and I did enjoy the film; I did not cry. The movie scores high for originality. I liked the concept of seeing the emotions interact with each other. I also found the segue showing the emotions in the mother and father to be quite hilarious. In the end, I think the storyline dragged on longer than needed, and therefore give the movie four stars.</review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/0/0a/Inside_Out_%282015_film%29_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yRUAzGQ3nSY</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Jurassic-World">
        <title>Jurassic World</title>
        <review>I've been a fan of Jurassic Park since the original in the early 90's. That being said, the subsequent sequels were all pretty poor. Because this was more of a reboot than a sequel my expectations were high while understanding what this movie is and isn't. For the summer blockbuster, fun-time adventure, it was fantastic. There were parts when it tried a little hard to be reminiscent of the past movies, but overall it was a fun ride. Chris Pratt is great, but probably underutilized in this role. Look for the Jimmy Buffet cameo. </review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/6/6e/Jurassic_World_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RFinNxS5KN4</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Max">
        <title>Max</title>
        <review>I didn't think it was possible to pack so many movie cliches into one movie. Enter Max. If this was sold as a children's movie more than a family movie, I would be less harsh.  Its hokey, corny and beyond acceptable-unrealism. The character roles are all over-exaggerated, it has it fair share of second-rate one-liners and you know the end from the beginning. I think the dog did a great job in the movie, and for that I give it two stars.</review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/d/d9/Max_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6EPPMCwD5bw</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Pitch-Perfect-2">
        <title>Pitch Perfect 2</title>
        <review>I really enjoyed the original Pitch Perfect. This sequel is a little hard to place for me. I really enjoyed the music and performances in the film, however everything else about the film was bad. I didn't like the storyline, character development and the comedy suffered, but like I said, I'll probably still download the music. For that, three stars.</review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/3f/Pitch_Perfect_2_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KBwOYQd21TY</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Furious-7">
        <title>Furious 7</title>
        <review>What types of expectations do you have for the seventh film in a series? It probably is not going to break out of the mold the series has already formed, and in the case of Furious 7, it did not. I like car those, so that's the main reason I continue to watch this series. Of course the tribute to Paul Walker is very touching at the end and help bring to light the importance of family. The storyline could be replaced by the same from any of the past three films and it would not have made a difference. The cars are cool. Vin Diesel is getting old. Overall three stars.</review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/b8/Furious_7_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Skpu5HaVkOc</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Insurgent">
        <title>Insurgent</title>
        <review>I didn't care much for the first film in the series, Divergent, and this one falls just as flat; maybe even more. The storyline is awful. The ending is completely awful. The characters are all emotional teenagers. The setting for the film is so unbelievable that I cannot get into the story no matter how hard I try. In the end, I wished I had spent my time doing something else. One star.</review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/af/Insurgent_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=suZcGoRLXkU</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Far-from-the-Madding-Crowd">
        <title>Madding Crowd</title>
        <review>Far from the Madding Crowd was a really interesting movie. I admit that I was intrigued the whole time. I'm not typically a fan of period pieces, however, this could have easily been modern-day England and little would have changed. I enjoyed the various characters and how they developed throughout the film. Also, this is the first movie I've seen with a love square, not triangle. I does lose points on two elements. I think it was a bit too long, and finally the resolution is too convenient for my taste. Overall three stars.</review>
        <img_url>http://t2.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSw0jAVU-AMygamdngTs5D3D88ELjTVXQ77per-DBumqLcijsh7</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WCm1XNVD_0c</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
    <movie name="Project-Almanac">
        <title>Project Almanac</title>
        <review>It is very apparent that I am no longer a teenager. I'm not even sure that I even enjoyed these overly party-hyped, non-stop drama, teenage movies when I was a teenager. That aside, let's talk about science. As with any si-fi you must suspend some amount of reality, but I think this goes beyond that scope; I'm not even talking about the time travel! I find it absolutely incredible that a few teenagers with little to no science background are able to aptly and quickly trouble-shoot complex time-travel problems, with a never-before seen time machine, and come up with garage-quality solution that unfailing work perfectly. I'm okay with time travel, but party-centric teens wildly smarted than Einstein, one star!</review>
        <img_url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/36/Project_Almanac_poster.jpg</img_url>
        <trailer_url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Yih-CxTWsw</trailer_url>
        <rating>{a}9733{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}{a}9734{b}</rating>
    </movie>
</Movies>